Guide to the Football Game Film Collection, 1934-2007 UA.13.01.0004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Football game film collection
1934-2007
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University Dept. of Athletics
UA.13.01.0004
155 Linear Feet
The Football Game Film Collection includes films of Duke football games from the 1930s through the 1990s created by Duke Athletics for use by coaches.
Arrangement
The materials in this collection are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The Football Game Films collection contains recordings of Duke football games created by Duke Athletics for the use of coaches and departmental staff. Recordings made before 1990 are largely on 16mm cellulose acetate film, black and white and with no audio; exceptions of color film or with included audio are noted in this guide where known. Recordings are grouped by individual game, titled by opponent, and include information on the game's outcome, score, and location, where known. Reference copies in other formats are included for a given game where they exist. Recordings made after 1989 are largely on video formats including VHS, BetaCam, and DVCam.
Also included are some compilations of games, highlights for certain players, and some recordings made from broadcast television.
Not every game played by Duke Football is included in this collection. Most games were recorded on several film reels, and some are missing. Many films have likely been edited. Additional information on location or game events may be included on the containers of individual recordings, or in the recordings themselves.
Access Restrictions
Use of audiotapes and videotapes from this collection requires the creation of reference copies. Reference copies for some materials may have been made, and if a reference copy exists, it is noted in this finding aid. To arrange for the creation of reference copies of other items, please contact University Archives staff. Although these recordings are now stored in a stable environment, their condition and playback quality is unknown.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Several accessions were combined into this collection guide. Materials were transferred from Duke Athletics over a period of years.
Football players -- North Carolina -- Durham; Football -- North Carolina -- Durham; Duke University. Department of Athletics; Duke University -- Football -- History -- 20th century
- Football Game Films
  - Unidentified, circa 1930s
    Scope and Contents
    Unknown outcome, score: unknown
    - Unidentified game coverage, circa 1930s; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 59, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0001)
    - Unidentified game coverage, circa 1930s; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 59, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0002)
  - UNC-VMI, 1934 August 01
    - UNC-VMI: Unidentified game coverage, 1934 August 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0003)
  - Ace Parker highlights, 1935 January 01
    Highlight reel
    - Game highlights, 1935 January 01; 16mm film: 3" reel (Box 67, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0004)
    - Game highlights, 1935 January 01; DVD (Box Unknown)
      Reference copy
    - Game highlights, 1935 January 01; DigiBeta (Box DM10)
      Duplication master
  - UNC-NCS, 1935 August 01
    - UNC-NCS: Unidentified game coverage, 1935 August 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0005)
  - National Highlights, 1935 August 01
    - Game highlights, 1935 August 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0006)
      No Duke coverage
  - Auburn, 1935 October 12
    Duke loss, score: 0-7
    - Duke vs. Auburn: Unidentified game coverage, 1935 October 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0007)
    - Duke vs. Auburn: Unidentified game coverage, 1935 October 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0008)
  - Tennessee, 1936, 1937, 1941, 1946, 1948-1949
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Game highlights, 1936, 1937, 1941, 1946, 1948-1949; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0009)
  - Colgate, 1936 September 26
    Duke win, score: 6-0
    - Duke vs. Colgate: Unidentified game coverage, 1936 September 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0010)
    - Duke vs. Colgate: Unidentified game coverage, 1936 September 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0011)
  - Clemson, 1936 October 10
    Duke win, score: 25-0
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Hall of Fame, 1936 October 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box missing, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0012)
  - Georgia Tech, 1936 October 17
    Duke win, score: 19-6
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Hall of Fame, 1936 October 17; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box missing, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0013)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1936 October 17; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 59, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0014)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1936 October 17; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 58, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0015)
      Preservation master
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1936 October 17; DVD
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1936 October 17; DigiBeta
  - Tennessee, 1936 October 24
    Duke loss, score: 13-15
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1936 October 24; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0016)
  - Davidson, 1937 October 02
    Duke win, score: 34-6
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Unidentified game coverage, 1937 October 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0017)
  - Tennessee, 1937 October 09
    Duke T, score: 0-0
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Hall of Fame, 1937 October 09; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box missing, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0018)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1937 October 09; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 63, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0019)
  - Colgate, 1937 October 23
    Duke win, score: 13-0
    - Duke vs. Colgate: Unidentified game coverage, 1937 October 23; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0020)
  - Washington and Lee, 1937 October 30
    Duke win, score: 43-0
    - Duke vs. Washington and Lee: Unidentified game coverage, 1937 October 30; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0021)
  - North Carolina, 1937 November 13
    Duke loss, score: 6-14
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1937 November 13; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0022)
  - NC State, 1937 November 20
    Duke win, score: 20-7
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1937 November 20; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0023)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1937 November 20; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 67, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0024)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1937 November 20; DVD
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1937 November 20; DigiBeta
  - Pittsburgh, 1937 November 27
    Duke loss, score: 0-10
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Unidentified game coverage, 1937 November 27; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0025)
  - Davidson, 1938 October 01
    Duke win, score: 27-0
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Unidentified game coverage, 1938 October 01; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 63, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0026)
  - Colgate, 1938 October 08
    Duke win, score: 7-0
    - Duke vs. Colgate: Unidentified game coverage, 1938 October 08; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 63, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0027)
  - Georgia Tech, 1938 October 15
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Hall of Fame, 1938 October 15; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box missing, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0028)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1938 October 15; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 63, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0029)
  - Wake Forest, 1938 October 22
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1938 October 22; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 63, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0030)
  - North Carolina, 1938 October 29
    Duke win, score: 14-0
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Hall of Fame, 1938 October 29; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box missing, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0031)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1938 October 29; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 58, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0032)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1938 October 29; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 59, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0033)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1938 October 29; DVD
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1938 October 29; DigiBeta
  - NC State, 1938 November 19
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1938 November 19; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 59, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0034)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1938 November 19; VHS
  - Southern California, 1939 January 02
    Duke loss, score: 3-7
    - Duke vs. Southern California: Unidentified game coverage, 1939 January 02; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 64, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0035)
    - Duke vs. Southern California: Unidentified game coverage, 1939 January 02; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 65, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0036)
      Master copy
    - Duke vs. Southern California: Unidentified game coverage, 1939 January 02; VHS
    - Duke vs. Southern California: Unidentified game coverage, 1939 January 02; DVD
    - Duke vs. Southern California: Unidentified game coverage, 1939 January 02; BetacamSP
  - Ace Parker highlights, 1939 August 01 - 1939 December 31
    - Highlights, 1939 August 01 - 1939 December 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0037)
  - Highlights, 1939-1941
    - Highlights, 1939-1941; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0038)
  - Pitt, 1939 October 14
    Duke loss, score: 13-14
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Unidentified game coverage, 1939 October 14; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0039)
  - Syracuse, 1939 October 21
    Duke win, score: 33-6
    - Duke vs. Syracuse: Unidentified game coverage, 1939 October 21; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0040)
  - Wake Forest, 1939 October 28
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1939 October 28; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 104, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0041)
  - North Carolina, 1939 November 18
    Duke win, score: 13-3
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1939 November 18; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0042)
  - VMI, 1940 September 28
    Duke win, score: 23-0
    - Duke vs. VMI: Unidentified game coverage, 1940 September 28; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 53, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0043)
  - Tennessee, 1940 October 05
    Duke loss, score: 0-13
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1940 October 05; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0044)
  - Colgate, 1940 October 19
    - Duke vs. Colgate: Unidentified game coverage, 1940 October 19; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0045)
  - Wake Forest, 1940 October 26
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1940 October 26; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0046)
  - Georgia Tech, 1940 November 02
    Duke win, score: 41-7
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Homecoming parade, 1940 November 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0047)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1940 November 02; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0048)
  - Davidson, 1940 November 09
    Duke win, score: 46-13
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Unidentified game coverage, 1940 November 09; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0049)
  - North Carolina, 1940 November 16
    Duke loss, score: 3-6
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1940 November 16; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0050)
  - NC State, 1940 November 23
    Duke win, score: 42-6
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1940 November 23; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 51, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0051)
  - Pittsburgh, 1940 November 30
    Duke win, score: 12-7
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Unidentified game coverage, 1940 November 30; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0052)
  - Tennessee, 1941 October 04
    Duke A, score: 19-0
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 October 04; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0053)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box missing, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0054)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 October 04; DVD
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 October 04; DVD
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 October 04; BetacamSP
  - Maryland, 1941 October 11
    Duke win, score: 50-0
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 October 11; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0055)
  - Colgate, 1941 October 18
    Duke win, score: 27-14
    - Duke vs. Colgate: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 October 18; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 152, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0056)
  - Pitt, 1941 October 25
    Duke win, score: 27-7
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 October 25; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 152, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0057)
  - Georgia Tech, 1941 November 01
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 November 01; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0058)
  - Davidson, 1941 November 08
    Duke win, score: 56-0
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 November 08; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 153, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0059)
  - North Carolina, 1941 November 15
    Duke win, score: 20-0
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 November 15; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 63, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0060)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 November 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0061)
      Color film.
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 November 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0062)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 November 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 66, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0063)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 November 15; DVD
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 November 15; DigiBeta
  - NC State, 1941 November 22
    Duke win, score: 55-6
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1941 November 22; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 153, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0064)
  - Oregon State, 1942 January 01
    Rose Bowl. Duke loss, score: 16-20
    - Duke vs. Oregon State: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 January 01; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 58, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0065)
    - Duke vs. Oregon State: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 January 01; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 60, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0066)
    - Duke vs. Oregon State: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 January 01; DVD
    - Duke vs. Oregon State: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 January 01; VHS
    - Duke vs. Oregon State: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 January 01; VHS
      Broadcast
  - Football Thrills, Fall 1942
    - Football Thrills: Unidentified game coverage, Fall 1942; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0067)
  - Davidson, 1942 September 26
    Duke win, score: 21-0
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 September 26; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0068)
  - Wake Forest, 1942 October 03
    Duke loss, score: 7-20
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 October 03; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0069)
  - Georgia Preflight, 1942 October 10
    Duke loss, score: 12-26
    - Duke vs. Georgia Preflight: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 October 10; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0070)
  - Pittsburgh, 1942 October 24
    Duke win, score: 28-0
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 October 24; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0071)
  - Georgia Tech, 1942 October 31
    Duke loss, score: 7-26
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 October 31; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0072)
  - Maryland, 1942 November 07
    Duke win, score: 42-0
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 November 07; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0073)
  - North Carolina, 1942 November 14
    Duke T, score: 13-13
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 November 14; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0074)
  - North Carolina, 1942 November 20
    Duke win, score: 27-6
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 November 20; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 67, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0075)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 November 20; DVD
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 November 20; DigiBeta
  - NC State, 1942 November 21
    Duke win, score: 47-0
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1942 November 21; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 54, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0076)
  - Football Thrills, Fall 1943
    - Football Thrills: Unidentified game coverage, Fall 1943; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0077)
  - Camp LaJeune, 1943 September 08
    Duke win, score: 40-0
    - Duke vs. Camp LaJeune: Unidentified game coverage, 1943 September 08; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0078)
  - Richmond, 1943 September 25
    Duke win, score: 61-0
    - Duke vs. Richmond: Unidentified game coverage, 1943 September 25; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 56, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0079)
  - Navy, 1943 October 09
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unidentified game coverage, 1943 October 09; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 56, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0080)
  - North Carolina, 1943 October 16
    Duke win, score: 14-7
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1943 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 103, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0081)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1943 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 103, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0082)
  - Georgia Tech, 1943 October 30
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1943 October 30; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0083)
  - NC State, 1943 November 06
    Duke win, score: 75-0
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1943 November 06; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 56, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0084)
  - Virginia, 1943 November 13
    Duke win, score: 49-0
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Unidentified game coverage, 1943 November 13; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 55, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0085)
  - North Carolina, 1943 November 20
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1943 November 20; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 104, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0086)
  - Richmond, 1944 September 23
    Duke win, score: 61-7
    - Duke vs. Richmond: Unidentified game coverage, 1944 September 23; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 60, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0087)
  - Pennsylvania, 1944 September 30
    Duke loss, score: 7-18
    - Duke vs. Pennsylvania: Unidentified game coverage, 1944 September 30; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 60, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0088)
  - N.C. Preflight, 1944 October 07
    Duke loss, score: 6-13
    - N.C. Preflight: Unidentified game coverage, 1944 October 07; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 56, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0089)
  - Navy, 1944 October 14
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unidentified game coverage, 1944 October 14; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 57, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0090)
  - Army, 1944 October 28
    Duke loss, score: 7-27
    - Duke vs. Army: Unidentified game coverage, 1944 October 28; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0091)
  - Georgia Tech, 1944 November 04
    Duke win, score: 1913
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1944 November 04; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 111, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0092)
  - Wake Forest, 1944 November 11
    Duke win, score: 34-0
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1944 November 11; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 56, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0093)
  - South Carolina, 1944 November 18
    Duke win, score: 34-7
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1944 November 18; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 56, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0094)
  - North Carolina, 1944 November 25
    Duke win, score: 33-0
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1944 November 25; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 56, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0095)
  - Alabama, 1945 January 01
    Sugar Bowl. Duke win, score: 29-26
    - Duke vs. Alabama: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 January 01; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 59, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0096)
    - Duke vs. Alabama: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 January 01; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 58, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0097)
      Commercial film with color and sound
    - Duke vs. Alabama: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 January 01; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 64, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0098)
    - Duke vs. Alabama: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 January 01; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 64, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0099)
    - Duke vs. Alabama: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 January 01; SVHS
  - Football Parade, Fall 1945
    - Football Parade, Fall 1945; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0100)
  - South Carolina, 1945 September 22
    Duke win, score: 60-0
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 September 22; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 57, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0101)
  - Bogue Field, 1945 September 29
    Duke win, score: 76-0
    - Bogue Field: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 September 29; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 57, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0102)
  - Navy, 1945 October 06
    Duke loss, score: 0-21
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 October 06; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 57, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0103)
  - Wake Forest, 1945 October 13
    Duke win, score: 26-19
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 October 13; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 58, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0104)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 October 13; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 59, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0105)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 October 13; DVD
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 October 13; DigiBeta
  - Army, 1945 October 27
    Duke loss, score: 13-48
    - Duke vs. Army: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 October 27; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 57, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0106)
  - Georgia Tech, 1945 November 03
    Duke win, score: 14-6
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 November 03; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 57, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0107)
  - NC State, 1945 November 10
    Duke win, score: 26-13
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 November 10; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 57, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0108)
  - North Carolina, 1945 November 24
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1945 November 24; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0109)
  - Football Parade, Fall 1946
    - Football Parade, Fall 1946; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0110)
  - Tennessee, 1946 October 05
    Duke loss, score: 7-12
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1946 October 05; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 61, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0111)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1946 October 05; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 61, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0112)
  - Navy, 1946 October 12
    Duke win, score: 21-6